Macsym

Kryvyi

Contact

Address:

Kievska, Ternopil, Ukraine

Phone:

+380 (98) 628 9298

Email:

lofi10617@gmail.com

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/maksymkryvyi-8ab076239

Skype:

live:.cid.e07bcb612fe88d1b

Language:

Russian - A English - C1

Skills:

React

React Native

Vue

Javascript

Typescript

HTML

CSS

SASS

Bootstrap

Node.js

Express.js

Laravel

MongoDB

MySQL

Summary

I have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and have been a **full-stack developer** since 2013. I have worked on 20+ projects and solved complex business problems with MERN & MEAN stacks in various industries including marketing, healthcare and eCommerce. I have consistently saved costs while increasing profits.

Skill Highlights

- User familiar UI/UX design
- Database Architecture
- RESTful API
- Soket IO
- Good communication

Experience

Senior Full Stack Developer - 03/2020 to 02/2022 OTAKOYI, L'viv, Ukraine

- Improved the front-end performance of a client application by 30%, reducing the time that users took to perform the tasks and consequently increasing the delivery and billing.
- Optimized data structures for MongoDB storage by creating, optimizing queries, indexing strategies, and aggregations.
- Contributed to 2 eCommerce applications and CRM application.

Full Stack Developer - 05/2016 to 07/2019 **INNCREWIN TECHNOLOGIES, Sudbrooke, United Kingdom**

- Collaborated with UI/UX team.
- Integrated and customized Material UI into React project.
- Configured and integrated API
- Contributed to 3 MERN stack applications.
- Contributed to 3 MEVN stack applications.

Education

Bachelor of Degree in **Computer Science** - 2013 **Kyiv National University of Technologies and Design**, Kyiv, Ukraine 2008 - 2013

Certification

Certified Web and Mobile Application Developer

Provider: SMTP Issued: January 2020 - Expires: January 2023